♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we’ve got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright
on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we’ll
withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there
when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we
will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko
stronger after all ♪
♪ Ah-ah-ah-ah! ♪
(INDISTINCT)
♪ Ah-mm-ah ah-ah! ♪
Hey, Odd, if you don’t mind,
I’m trying to study!
♪ Mm-mm-mm-mm! Mm-mm! ♪
Yeah!
♪ Ah-ah-ah-ah-- ♪
Cut that out! Maybe you forgot,
but we’ve got a test tomorrow!
So stop!
Huh? What did you say?
I can’t hear a thing!
I said I want to study, Odd!
What’s the sense of you studying?
Whatever you do, you’re still
gonna a zero in physics,
so why not listen to what I
downloaded from the web?
Go on, listen to it!
It sure beats studying!
It’s the cool music!
And nobody knows who wrote it, either!
It’s an MP3 file, and it’s free!
It’s a pop rock revolution!
You want a revolution?
Okay, I’ll give you one.
You don’t think of anyone
but yourself, and I’m fed up!
Hey, where you going?
To Jeremie’s room.
At least he knows you need
peace and quiet when you’re studying.
He’s not like you, selfish!
Don’t worry, Kiwi. He’ll get over it.
♪ Hm-hm hm-hm-hm ♪
♪ I’m so glad when you’re bad! ♪
(KNOCKING)
Ulrich? Uh, what’s the matter?
Odd and his music are driving me nuts.
You’re not into heavy metal, pop, funk?
Not when I have to study for an exam.
Is it okay if I study in your room?
Sure.
I can even give you
some help if you want.
I could sure use some.
♪ So, so glad when you’re
really ba-ah-ah-ad! ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh! Ah-ah-ah! ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mm-mm
mm-mm-mm! ♪
(BARKS)
Time to get up, Ulrich!
Too tired…
Do I have to remind you
you have a test this morning?
I didn’t get a lot of sleep.
How come?
Well, I’ll tell you how come.
Oh, Aelita!
Oh, Aelita,
you’re in my dreams!
I can’t wait until--
Shh! She’ll hear you!
Between you and Odd,
I can’t study or sleep.
Hey, you’re not gonna tell anybody, huh?
Promise, Romeo.
Let’s get some breakfast.
Okay, but not with Odd.
He made me so mad last night.
Whatever you say.
Have you finished the layout?
Yeah, sure.
How come Odd’s still not here?
I couldn’t care less.
What’s the song’s name?
The title is “Glad When You’re Bad.”
I honestly can’t believe
how unhip you guys are!
You’re a couple of real losers.
You oughta go out once in a while!
Well then fill us in, Sissi.
What kind of music is it? Is it R&B?
R&B? Why not waltz music
while you’re at it…
Odd ought to be here.
Maybe he didn’t wake up.
Forget about it. It’s his problem.
Hey, chill out, you’re
making such a big deal
over a little bit
of loud music, Ulrich.
We can’t let him miss his exam.
Yes, we can.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
Hi.
Odd isn’t here?
No, and I’m beginning to worry.
Did you check in his room?
Not yet. We’re gonna do that right now.
Right, Ulrich?
No, we’ll be late for the exam.
Not if we hurry.
Keep me posted, okay?
He sang that same
dumb song over and over.
And look. Now he’s fast asleep.
Let’s wake him up.
Hey Odd, get up, will you?
Hey!
If this is a joke, it’s a bad one.
And we’re gonna be late!
Something’s wrong!
Odd? Odd!
This isn’t a joke!
Odd? Odd? Can you hear me?
Call the hospital!
And tell them it’s very, very urgent.
Hello? This is the
junior high school here.
We need an ambulance immediately.
His blood pressure
and his heartbeat are slow.
I don’t understand.
If we add up the resistances
in a continuous circuit,
the intensity of the current diminishes.
In a derivative circuit, however,
the current produced by the generator
is equal to the sum of the intensities
in the derivative circuit branches.
Odd?
Sorry, Miss Hertz, it’s…
it’s Odd, he--
Yumi!
All right, settle down.
What’s the matter with him?
Is it serious? Well, is it?
His heart’s beating very slowly.
XANA!
XANA’s not capable of
attacking human beings directly.
If only I’d stayed with him last night,
this wouldn’t have happened.
We had a big fight,
and I slept in Jeremie’s room.
How could you have known that?
I’m staying with him!
I’m sorry, Ulrich, but I can’t
permit you to leave the school grounds.
I’m staying with Odd.
Ulrich, get away from that ambulance!
That is not the right way to help him!
I don’t care.
I can’t let him be taken away like this.
Alright, you can go.
I want to go with him too!
Are you crazy?
What if XANA launches an attack?
We’ll stay in contact.
Call me if there’s the slightest problem.
We can’t handle many more emergencies.
Ulrich, stop. You’re not to blame.
No, it’s all my fault.
No, it’s not.
Even if you had been there,
you couldn’t have changed anything.
I’ll go get us a soda.
It’ll do us both good.
I’m gonna go see Odd.
I’ll see you in his room.
Doctor, two new cases have just arrived.
40 heartbeats a minute.
Can you take them?
Send them to the Johnson’s hospital.
Doctor Miller is wanted in cardiology.
Aelita?
Jeremie, how’s everything going?
Not good.
Odd’s in a coma, it’s really weird.
His heart has almost stopped beating.
Oh, no!
No one knows what to do,
and the weirdest thing of all
is that Odd may not be
the only one hit by the illness.
Bizarre.
Do you think XANA’s capable
of creating a disease?
I can’t believe he was actually able
to attack humans directly.
Looks like he might’ve found a way.
Anyway, I’d better warn Ulrich and Yumi.
Meanwhile, see if you feel any pulsations.
Okay.
Sissi? Are you okay?
Sissi!
Hey, Sissi!
Oh, no!
Ulrich, I just spoke to Aelita.
She’s gonna try and see if XANA
is the cause of our problem.
If he did this, I can’t figure out how.
What I do know is that going to Lyoko
is the only way to save him, so let’s go.
We’ll get you out of this.
I swear we will.
Oh, no. XANA’s activated a tower.
Hey, Jeremie, how’s Odd?
His heart’s getting weaker and weaker!
Sissi’s got the same symptoms.
It’s spreading!
And it could be an epidemic
started by XANA!
Did you reach Aelita?
Yeah, I did. Get over to the factory, fast!
(CLASSICAL MUSIC)
(KNOCKING)
Oh, no! Sissi!
This way.
There. Set her down. Gently.
(“GLAD WHEN YOU’RE BAD” PLAYS)
Oh no, my head! That horrible song!
Dorothy!
The music! It’s definitely the music!
Connecting. Connecting.
Aelita, we’re in the lab.
Better hurry.
The pulsations are getting stronger.
The activated tower can’t be too far away.
Any monsters around?
Not yet, no.
Ulrich’s coming soon.
Stay where you are.
Okay, I’ll wait here.
Yumi!
Jeremie, it’s the song that’s causing it!
What do you mean, the song?
I don’t understand.
It is! It’s the song “Glad When You’re Bad!”
Oh, no!
I think that’s the song Odd
downloaded from the web yesterday!
XANA’s using the media
for maximum coverage.
He’s formatted the song, and now,
he’s spreading it all over!
A deadly melody.
Considering what it’s done to Odd,
we better deactivate the tower.
Send Yumi as soon as she gets here.
I’ll send you north to the mountains.
Transfer Ulrich.
Scanner Ulrich.
Virtualization.
Ulrich!
We’ve got to get
to the activated tower fast.
Look, it’s there. You see?
Attention, please.
All available cardiologists
are urgently requested
to report to the flemming wing.
Okay.
We’re at the tower.
There it is.
This morning, we’ve been
swamped with calls
warning us of a mysterious epidemic.
For an update, let’s got to our reporter
Bill Amster who is on the scene.
-Bill?
-Thank you, Olivia.
As soon as news of the
first cases were announced,
I went to the neighborhood, and
things here are dramatic to say the least.
For now, it seems that the authorities
can’t quote a figure on the number of people
who have actually been
stricken by the illness.
The victims seem to be
under the spell of the disease
whose origins are unknown,
and whose outcome could be fatal.
That’s what you think.
Public health officials
are presently on the scene.
Hiyah!
No monsters anywhere.
That’s suspicious.
Ah, there you are.
Aelita, take cover somewhere.
Hiyah!
Ulrich!
Ulrich, you’re out of bounds
for three minutes.
Everything okay on Lyoko?
Not really.
Ulrich’s frozen solid and Aelita’s alone.
I’m ready to go.
To the mountains.
Transfer Yumi.
Here we go.
Scanner Yumi.
Virtualization!
Ulrich, 30 seconds to go.
Stay behind me, Aelita.
I’ll handle them.
How much longer, Jeremie?
He’s coming.
Go!
Glad to see ya.
Better stay alert!
Two Bloks are on their way.
That one’s yours, Yumi.
Well done.
According to the public health department,
the very first cases were discovered
at Kadic Junior High School.
Huh?
[“Glad When You’re Bad” plays]
No!
Jeremie, do you read me?
Jeremie!
Yumi, you and Aelita run to the tower.
You’re crazy!
You’ll never make it all alone!
Who said I would be alone?
Triangulate!
Position! Go!
Oh, no!
What!
Aelita!
Hiyah!
Got to enter the coordinates
for the return trip.
Launching!
I did it.
I did it!
Oh, no! Yumi!
No, Aelita!
Don’t worry about me, go on!
Ah!
♪ Mhmm! ♪
♪ Da-dat-dat-dat-eh-ah! ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm ♪
Yeah!
♪ Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha! ♪
Hey, Odd, come on.
I’m trying to study.
What’s the sense in studying?
You’re gonna get a zero!
I’ve heard that twice already.
That’s enough.
Hey, listen to what I
downloaded from the web!
It’s out of sight!
“Under my Cover” by R.U. Fleggmatic!
It’s incredible!
Later, okay?
For the time being, I’d like to study.
And as for you, I wouldn’t say no
to your helping me a little.
You’re so good in physics.
That’s right! And if you want help,
the reincarnation of Einstein
is willing to give a lesson
to a sawdust-filled head!
And I’ll listen to your song afterwards.
Mmm…you don’t really have to.
Actually, it’s pretty mainstream.
It’s something that…
what I mean is…
It’s the kind of song
a machine might have written?
Yeah, that’s right.
See? You know a lot about music!
♪ Mm-m-m-m-mm ♪
So, you gonna help me or what?
Just a second!
Yeah, yeah.
We’ll see about that.